Inventory of the Frank Snowden Hopkins Papers 1951-1993
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Frank Snowden Hopkins Papers, 1951-1993.
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Mss. 84 H77
1,705 items.
Written works, published and unpublished, of Frank Snowden Hopkins, journalist, diplomat, and vice-president of the World Future Society.
Frank Snowden Hopkins.
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
Acc. No. 84-36; Gift: 25 items, July 1984.
Acc. No. 86-15; Gift: 1 item, April 1986.
Acc. No. 89-38; Gift: 1 item, September 1989.
Acc. No. 89.55; Gift: 1 item, 29 November 1989.
Acc. No. 1993.48; Gift: 1 item, 19 July 1993.
Acc. No. 1994.64A; Gift: ca. 100 items, 22 August 1994.
Acc. No. 2000.23; Gift: 1,376 items, 3 June 2000.
Biographical/Historical Information
Frank Snowden Hopkins was born 8 March 1908 in Gloucester County, Virginia, the son of Nicholas Snowden Hopkins and Selina Lloyd (Hepburn) Hopkins. He graduated with an B. A. from the College of William and Mary and received his M. A. from Columbia University. Hopkins worked for newspapers as a reporter, personnel and labor relations director and for the Maryland Drydock Company. Hopkins entered the U. S. State Department in 1945.
Biography Timeline
1908 Born to Nicholas Snowden and Selina Lloyd (Hepburn) in Gloucester County, Virginia
1927 Graduated (B. A.) from College of William and Mary; Phi Beta Kappa
1928 Received M. A. from Columbia University
1929 Editorial Assistant for D. Appleton and Company
1930- 31 Reporter for Minneapolis Star
1933- 36 Reporter for Richmond Times-Dispatch
1934 20 October, Married Ruth Hazen
1936-38 Reporter for the Baltimore Sun
1939 Nieman Fellowship to Harvard
1941- 45 Personnel and Labor Relations Director, Maryland Drydock Company
1945 Enters State Department
1946 Moved to Washington, D. C.
1947-51 Assistant Director, Foreign Service Institute
1951 Faculty member, Army War College
1952-55 Public Relations Officer, Stuttgart, West Germany
1956-58 Deputy Director, UNESCO Relations Staff
1958- 60 Consul, Martinique, French West Indies
1960-63 U. S. Consul General, Melbourne, Australia
1963-64 Speech Writer, State Department-Board of Examiners for Foreign Service
1964-67 Director of Fulbright Exchange Program, State Department Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs
1967-68 Consultant on long- range foreign policy, Policy Planning Council
1968 Retired from Government Service
1968-70 Joined World Future Society
1970-78 Coordinator of Chapter Affairs, World Future Society
1975-84 Vice President of World Future Society
1995 Died
Scope and Content Information
Written works, published and unpublished, of Frank Snowden Hopkins, journalist, diplomat, and vice-president of the World Future Society. The collection contains articles written about the Foreign Service, policy papers written for the United States State Department, articles written for the World Future Society, family histories and biographies, a reminiscence of the College of William and Mary in the 1920's, and an unpublished manuscript of a novel promoting the goals and principles of the World Future Society.
Arrangement
Organization
This collection is organized into eleven series. Series 1 contains family histories and biographies; Series 2 contains speeches by Hopkins; Series 3 contains essays prepared for U.S. State Department; Series 4 contains articles by Hopkins pertaining to the foreign service; Series 5 contains articles by Hopkings pertaining to the World Future Society; and Series 6-11 contain additions to the collection.
Arrangement
The collection is organized by subject.
Controlled Access Terms
Index Terms
Subjects:
College of William and Mary--History--20th century.; Forecasting.
Organizations:
World Future Society.
Contents List
- Reminiscences by Hopkins of William and Mary in the 1920s, c. 1980., 1 item. (Folder 1)
  Series 1: Family Histories and Biographies
- Family histories and biographies, 1972-1976., 7 items. (Folder 2-8)
  - The Story of Ruth, Part 1, a biographical sketch by Hopkins of his wife, Ruth Hazen Hopkins (1906-1974), Ca. 1975., 1 item. (Folder 2)
  - The Story of Ruth, Part 2, the continuation of a biographical sketch by Hopkins of his wife, Ruth Hazen Hopkins (1906-1974), Ca. 1975., 1 item. (Folder 3)
  - My Hopkins and Snowden Ancestors, a history by Hopkins of his father's families, respectively, 1976., 1 item. (Folder 4)
  - The Ninety-Two Years of Selina Z. Hopkins, (1878-1970), a biographical sketch of their mother by Hopkins, his brother and two sisters, 1973-1974., 1 item. (Folder 5)
  - The Hepburn Family of Kent County, Maryland (1665-1932), a family history by Hopkins and others, 1975., 1 item. (Folder 6)
  - The Hepburn Family of Kent County, Maryland, Part II: Appendices to the Text, by Hopkins and others, 1976., 1 item. (Folder 7)
  - Carl Withers, (1900-1970), a memoir prepared by Hopkins and others of his classmate and friend, 1972., 1 item. (Folder 8)
  Series 2: Speeches by Hopkins
- Speeches by Hopkins, 1952-1967., 4 items. (Folder 9-11)
  - A Foreign Affairs Service for the 1960s, a speech by Hopkins delivered, February 15, 1952., 2 items. (Folder 9)
    Cover letter accompanies it.
  - A Senior Foreign Affairs Officer, a speech delivered by Hopkins while Consul-General at Melbourne, Australia (1960-1963), Ca. 1960., 1 item. (Folder 10)
  - American Foreign Policy, 1975-2000: The Role of Educational and Cultural Diplomacy in Tomorrow's World, a speech delivered by Hopkins on August 8, 1967, 1967., 1 item. (Folder 11)
  Series 3: Essays Prepared For U. S. State Department
- Essays prepared for U. S. State Department, 1967-1968., 3 items. (Folder 12-14)
  - International Education in Tomorrow's World, an essay prepared by Hopkins for the Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs, U.S. State Department, 1967., 1 item. (Folder 12)
  - American Educational Assistance to Less Developed Countries, an action plan written by Hopkins as a sequel to the essay in Folder 12, 1967., 1 item. (Folder 13)
  - Communications Satellites and International Understanding, an essay prepared by Hopkins for the U.S. State Department, 1968., 1 item. (Folder 14)
  Series 4: Articles by Hopkins Pertaining To "The Foreign Service Journal"
- Articles by Hopkins pertaining to the Foreign Service Journal, 1951-1969., 5 items. (Folder 15-18)
  - Foreign Service Journal, 28 (October 1951), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins', How to Get Ahead in the Foreign Service, 1951., pages 24-26, 52. 1 item. (Folder 15)
  - Foreign Service Journal, 37 (June 1960), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins', Individuality in the Foreign Service, 1960., pages 21-23. 1 item. (Folder 16)
  - Foreign Service Journal, 39 (March 1962), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins', Planning for Foreign Policy Leadership, 1962., pages 21-26. 1 item. (Folder 17)
  - Foreign Service Journal, 39 (November 1962), containing Hopkins' Executive Ability in the Foreign Service, pages 21-24; and Looking Ahead to the Year 2001, by Hopkins, a reprint from Foreign Service Journal, 46 (January 1969), pages 32-33, 41, 1962-1969., 2 items. (Folder 18)
  Series 5: Articles By Hopkins Pertaining To The World Future Society
- Four articles by Hopkins for the World Future Society and its communicative organs, the WFS Bulletin and The Futurist, 1973-1983., 4 items. (Folder 19)
- Hopkins, Frank Snowden, The Man Who Lived Twice, an unpublished, typed manuscript novel promoting the goals and principles of the World Future Society, C. 1980., 1 item. TMS 1. (Box 2)
  Series 6: Addition to Collection, 1989.38
- Memoir of N. Snowden Hopkins (1877-1937) by Frank Snowden Hopkins, January 1, 1988., 32, 2 pages with 8 pages of photographs. (Othertype 1989.38)
  Series 7: Addition to Collection, 1889.55
- The Powell and Lloyd Families of Alexandria, Virginia, by Frank Snowden Hopkins, 1988., 33, A-23, 4 pages plus 13 pages of photographs. (Othertype 1889.55)
  A family history of the maternal ancestors of his mother, Selina Lloyd Hepburn Hopkins, of Gloucester County, VA, a descendant of the Alexandria merchants Cuthbert Powell (1775-1849) and John Lloyd.
  Series 8: Addition to Collection, 1993.48
- Autobiographical essay, of Frank Snowden Hopkins, March 8, 1993. (Othertype 1993.48.)
  Tracing his career through education, journalism, diplomatic service, and two marriages.
  Series 9: Addition to Collection, 1994.64A
- Frank Snowden Hopkins papers addition, 1966-1990. (Othertype 1994.64A)
  Material contains speeches and essays.
  - Taking Byzantine History in the Nieman Program, 1989., 1 item. (Folder 1)
    Hopkins' personal account of a Byzantine History class he took at Harvard as a Nieman fellow in 1938.
  - A Discussion of Personal Philosophy, 1990., 1 item. (Folder 2)
    An essay by Hopkins in which he discusses his humanist philosophy.
  - The Family of Nicholas Snowden Hopkins, 1990., 1 item. (Folder 3)
    A history of the family of Hopkins' father, Nicholas Snowden Hopkins (1877-1937), beginning with Hopkins' great-grandparents.
  - The Next Forty Years, 20 November 1966., 1 item. (Folder 4)
    Text of a speech delivered by Hopkins at the University of Pittsburgh, 20 November 1966.
  - Preparing for the Year 2000: The Challenge to American Education, 18 February 1967., 1 item. (Folder 5)
    Text of a speech delivered by Hopkins at the Conference of the American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education in Chicago, 18 February 1967.
  - The Good Life in America's Future, 5 April 1967., 1 item. (Folder 6)
    Text of a speech delivered by Hopkins at Valparaiso University, 5 April 1967.
  - American Foreign Policy, 1975-2000: The Role of Educational and Cultural Diplomacy in Tomorrow's World, 8 August 1967., 1 item. (Folder 7)
    Text of a speech delivered by Hopkins at the Institute on World Affairs, San Diego, California, 8 August 1967.
  - The Next Thirty Years, 26 May 1968., 1 item. (Folder 8)
    Text of a speech delivered by Hopkins at the Indiana University of Pennsylvania, 26 May 1968.
  - America in Tomorrow's World, 18 February 1971., 1 item. (Folder 9)
    Text of a speech delivered by Hopkins at Saint Louis University, 18 February 1971.
  - Report on the Future, 18 September 1971., 1 item. (Folder 10)
    Text of a speech delivered by Hopkins to the newspaper publishers of Pennsylvania in Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 18 September 1971.
  - Some Thoughts for Professional Educators, 24-25 July 1973., 1 item. (Folder 11)
    Text of a speech delivered by Hopkins at the World Future Society's summer conference on Learning for Tomorrow: A Look at Education Futures, George Washington University, 24-25 July 1973.
  - Opening statement for the seminar on The Nature of Time in the Twenty-first Century at the Sixth General Assembly of the World Future Society, Washington, D.C., 18 July 1989, delivered by Hopkins, 18 July 1989., 1 item. (Folder 12)
  - International Education in Tomorrow's World: The Challenge to American Diplomacy, 1967., 1 item. (Folder 13)
  - Looking Ahead to the Year 2000, 1967., 1 item. (Folder 14)
    Manuscript of an article written for publication in which Hopkins lays out a methodology for planning an American foreign policy to cope with foreseeable international problems.
  - The United States in the Year 2000: A Proposal for the Study of the American Future, 1967., 1 item. (Folder 15)
  - Some Major Issues of the International Future, 1974., 1 item. (Folder 16)
    A discussion of global problems and the need for planning to confront such problems.
  - The Future of Futures Research, 1976 [?]., 1 item. (Folder 17)
    A discussion of the methodology of future study.
  - Human Intelligence: Do We Need More of It to Survive?, 1983., 1 item. (Folder 18)
    A review of Robert Jastrow's The Enchanted Loom and Morton Hunt's The Universe Within: A New Science Explores the Human Mind.
  - The Fortieth Anniversary of UNESCO, 1986., 1 item. (Folder 19)
    Hopkins outlines a vision for the role of UNESCO in the future.
  - America's Future, or Present Prospects?, 1987 [?]., 1 item. (Folder 20)
    A manuscript of review of Douglas Caddy's Exploring America's Future. The review was published in the British journal Futures.
  - Historical Trends and the Human Future, 1990., 1 item. (Folder 21)
    An argument for human history as a process of everything growing closer together and a discussion of the ramifications of such a process.
  - Essays concerning the future role of the World Future Society, 1988-1993., 2 items. (Folder 22)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, The Sesquicentennial of a Rural American, 1845-1995: A Family and Personal Memoir, 1983., Unpublished, typed manuscript, pages 1-78. 1 item. (Folder 23)
    A largely autobiographical memoir.
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, The Sesquicentennial of a Rural American, 1845-1995: A Family and Personal Memoir, 1983., Unpublished, typed manuscript, pages 79-175. 1 item. (Folder 24)
    A largely autobiographical memoir. Chapter 5 includes reminiscences of William and Mary in the 1920s.
  - Four short essays written by Hopkins reprinted from The World Future Society Bulletin and The Futurist, 1975-1985., 4 items. (Folder 25)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, The Sesquicentennial of a Rural American, 1845-1995: A Family and Personal Memoir, 1983., Unpublished, typed manuscript, pages 176-257. 1 item. (Folder 26)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, The Sesquicentennial of a Rural American, 1845-1995: A Family and Personal Memoir, 1983., Unpublished, typed manuscript, pages 258-354. 1 item. (Folder 27)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, A World to Plan for: American Foreign Policy, 1976-2001, 1976., Unpublished, typed manuscript, chapters I-IV. 1 item. (Folder 28)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, A World to Plan for: American Foreign Policy, 1976-2001, 1976., Unpublished, typed manuscript, chapters V-VI. 1 item. (Folder 29)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, A World to Plan for: American Foreign Policy, 1976-2001, 1976., Unpublished, typed manuscript, chapters VII-VIII (chapter IX missing). 1 item. (Folder 30)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, A World to Plan for: American Foreign Policy, 1976-2001, 1976., Unpublished, typed manuscript, chapters X-XII. 1 item. (Folder 31)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, A World to Plan for: American Foreign Policy, 1976-2001, 1976., Unpublished, typed manuscript, chapters XIII-XV. 1 item. (Folder 32)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, A World to Plan for: American Foreign Policy, 1976-2001, 1976., Unpublished, typed manuscript, chapters XVI-XVIII. 1 item. (Folder 33)
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, A World to Plan for: American Foreign Policy, 1976-2001, 1976., Unpublished, typed manuscript, chapters XIX-XX. 1 item. (Folder 34)
  - The United State in the Year 2000: A Proposal for the Study of the American Future, 1967., 1 item. (Folder 35)
    Reprinted from The American Sociologist, Vol. 2, No. 3, August 1967.
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, Waverly, 1971., 1 item. (Folder 36)
    A history and personal reminiscences of Hopkins' boyhood home in Gloucester County, Virginia. GeHardit Press, Gloucester, Virginia.
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, A Memoir of N. Snowden Hopkins, 1988., 1 item. Typeset and bound, with reprinted photographs. (Folder 37)
    A biographical memoir of Hopkins' father, N. Snowden Hopkins (1877-1937).
  - Hopkins, Frank Snowden, The Powell and Lloyd Families of Alexandria, Virginia, 1988., 1 item. Typeset and bound, with reprinted photographs. (Folder 38)
    A family history of the maternal ancestors of Hopkins' mother, Selina Lloyd Hepburn Hopkins (1878-1970).
  - The Futurist(August 1968), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins', Stuart Chase Envisions the Most Probable World, August 1968., pages 82-83. 1 item. (Folder 39)
    A review of Chase's The Most Probable World.
  - The Futurist (December 1968), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' Biologist Would Penalize Parents, December 1968., page 119. 1 item. (Folder 40)
    A review of Paul Ehrlich's The Population Bomb.
  - The Futurist (February 1969), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' Technology vs. Ethics: Must 'Can' Imply 'Ought'?, February 1969., page 13. 1 item. (Folder 41)
  - The Futurist(August 1969), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' Future Research: An International Effort, a review of Mankind 2000, August 1969., pages 105-106. 1 item. (Folder 42)
    A book of essays on future subjects.
  - The Futurist, October 1969., page 128. 1 item. (Folder 43)
    Containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' review on John McHale's The Future of the Future.
  - The Futurist, December 1969., 1 item. (Folder 44)
    Containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' Eurich Foresees Restructuring of College System. A review of Alvin Eurich's Reforming American Education.
  - The Futurist(April 1970), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' Courage Toward Utopia, April 1970., pages 65-66. 1 item. (Folder 45)
    A review of Georg Picht's Mut zur Utopie: Die Grossen Zukunftsaufgaben.
  - The Futurist(February 1970), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' The Rise of Technological Man, February 1970., pages 12-13. 1 item. (Folder 46)
    A review of Victor C. Ferkiss' Technological Man: The Myth and the Reality.
  - William and Mary, the Alumni Gazette(May 1970), containing Frank S. Hopkins' In Thirty Years, May 1970., pages 4-6. 1 item. (Folder 47)
  - The Futurist(June 1970), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' review of Lester R. Brown's Seeds of Change: The Green Revolution and Development in the 1970s, June 1970., pages 103-104. 1 item. (Folder 48)
  - The Futurist(February 1971), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' Futurism, Robotism, or Destruction, February 1971., pages 23-24. 1 item. (Folder 49)
    A review of Ossip K. Flechtheim's Futurologie: Der Kampf um die Zukunft.
  - The Futurist(April 1985), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' review of Stuart M. Speiser's How to End the Nuclear Nightmare, April 1985., page 48. 1 item. (Folder 50)
  - The Futurist(June 1985), containing Frank Snowden Hopkins' Psychotherapy for Nations: An Alternative to the Arms Race, June 1985., page 44. 1 item. (Folder 51)
    A review of Roger Walsh's Staying Alive: The Psychology of Human Survival.
  Series 10: Addition to Collection, 2000.23
- Frank Snowden Hopkins papers addition, 1930-1990. (Othertype 2000.23)
  - Articles, correspondence, and memorabilia concerning Hopkins' years in the Foreign Service, 1946-1969. (Box-folder 1:1-87)
    - Biographical sketches and résumés for Frank Snowden Hopkins., 21 items. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Letters outlining views on Foreign service and cultural policy and program., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:2)
      Includes essay on The Background of World Politics by Dr. William page Maddox.
    - Correspondence and notes concerning plans and analyses of Foreign Service policy, 1946-1955., 8 items. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Letters relating to Foreign Service, including biographical data, 1950-1952., 35 items. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Correspondence pertaining to Foreign Service assignment in Germany, 1951-1955., 19 items. (Box-folder 1:5)
    - Press releases concerning Foreign Service assignment to Germany, 1952-1955., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:6)
    - Letters, notes, postcards, and memorabilia from Foreign Service assignment in Germany, 1955-1956., 30 items. (Box-folder 1:7)
    - Correspondence pertaining to Foreign Service, 1957., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:8)
    - Letters pertaining to Foreign Service in Martinique, French West Indies, 1959-1960., 33 items. (Box-folder 1:9)
    - Personal letters and photographs from Foreign Service assignment in Martinique, 1959-1960., 24 items. (Box-folder 1:10)
    - Correspondence regarding fellowship to The Center of Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1959-1963., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:11)
    - Newspaper articles about Hopkins during his Consulship in Australia, 1960-1963., 14 items. (Box-folder 1:12)
    - Correspondence relating to Foreign Service in Australia, 1963-1968., 25 items. (Box-folder 1:13)
    - Correspondence and reactions to Hopkins's articles and speeches on The American Future, 1966-1968., 25 items. (Box-folder 1:14)
    - Correspondence relating to Foreign Service in Australia and relating to articles about Australia, 1967-1968., 36 items. (Box-folder 1:15)
    - Correspondence concerning the creation of an International Education Administration, 1967., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:16)
    - Correspondence and writings pertaining to The Application of Instructional Television to the Educational Problems of Less Developed Countries, 1967-1968., 19 items. (Box-folder 1:17)
    - Letter to Ted Eliot concerning Foreign Service categories, 20 November 1968., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:18)
    - Essay in The American Foreign Service Journal, Problems and Training of Foreign Service Clerical Personnel, December 1945., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:19)
    - Essay on A Suggested Approach to the Problem of Improving the Administrative Efficiency of the Department of State, Parts I and II, 17 January 1946., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:20)
    - Essay and summary on Diagnosis of Present Difficulties in the Department of State, 17 April 1946., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:21)
    - Essay on Objectives of the Division of Management and Planning, 1 August 1946., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:22)
    - Essay on A Critical Appraisal of the Written Entrance Examinations for the Foreign Service, 11 September 1946., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:23)
    - Article written for Harper's Magazine Toward a Better Foreign Service, 12 November 1946., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:24)
    - Article on Training needs of the Foreign Service, 1946., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:25)
    - Article for The American Foreign Service Journal, Some Suggestions for the In-Service Training Program of Foreign Service Officers, 1946., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:26)
    - Essay entitled The Embassy of the Future, 21 March 1946., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:27)
    - Essay entitled A Description of the Paris and London Embassies, 5 June 1946., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:28)
    - Address of Welcome to the Foreign Service trainees, 1 July 1946., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:29)
    - Essay entitled New Insights into Human Motivation, Parts I and II, 1946., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:30)
    - Essay entitled Is Diplomacy a Profession?, 26 June 1946., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:31)
    - Essays and correspondence concerning the Foreign Service Institute, 1946-55., 12 items. (Box-folder 1:32)
    - Essay entitled The American Government Employee Abroad: Some Suggestions on Conduct and Relationships in Foreign Countries, ca. 1947., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:33)
    - Address to University Vocational Information Council for Women Students, Ohio State University, 14 February 1947., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:34)
    - Article in The American Foreign Service Journal, Psychological Tensions in the Foreign Service, March 1947., 2 items. Original typed copy and published version. (Box-folder 1:35)
    - Article in The American Foreign Service Journal, Should the Foreign Service Officer Specialize?, July 1947., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:36)
    - Essays on Educational Preparation for the Foreign Service and Education for the New Diplomacy, 1947-48., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:37)
    - Biographical and analytical essay on Why I Like the State Department, ca. 1948., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:38)
    - Article for Public Administration Review, volume III, number 2, Training Responsibilities in the Department of State, Spring 1948., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:39)
    - Essay entitled The Foreign Service Officer in Washington, The American Foreign Service Journal, November 1948., 2 items. Includes draft and published copy. (Box-folder 1:40)
    - Essay entitled Career Classroom, The New York Times Magazine, 5 December 1948., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:41)
    - Essay entitled The Foreign Service Institute Today, 6 December 1948., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:42)